<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><resources>	<string name="hello">Hello World, Click Me!</string>	<string name="app_name">Fluffle</string>	<string name="test">test</string>	<string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>		<string name="Game_Menu">Bunny Garden</string>	<string name="Profile_Menu">Profile</string>	<string name="Leaderboards_Menu">Leaderboards</string>	<string name="Cam_Menu">Live Bunny Cam!</string>	<string name="About_Menu">About Fluffle</string>	<string name="AboutFluffleText">Here is everything you would ever want to know about fluffle.		\n\nYou start with one bunny.  Tap it to select it.  This will show you info about the bunny.  		Then tap the feed button to feed your bunny a carrot.  That will make it grow.  It is size 1 to start.  		After 10 carrots it will be size 2.  Each size takes more carrots.  Large bunnies are easier to breed.		\n\nYou get carrots every day you play.  You can also buy them in the carrot store as an in-app purchase.		\n\nIf you want more bunnies, you can adopt them for carrots from the adoption center.  You can also get 		bunnies by breeding them.  You need a male and female of the same breed and size to have babies.  		Happy bunnies and large bunnies are more likely to breed.  Note that a mommy bunny can only have one baby per day.		\n\nYou can also TRADE bunnies with  your friends.  To do this, tap the bunny and press the TOSS button.  		This will show a barcode.  Then have your friend press the CATCH button on their screen to start the camera.  		If they point it at your barcode, they will get your bunny!  Try it, it is super fun.  		You can also trade bunnies over a video call.		\n\nWhat else?  Click the bunny\'s name to rename it.  Every bunny needs a name.  You can also go to the profile 		to set your own name.</string>		<string name="AboutFloppsyText">Floppsy is my bunny.  She is a Mini-lop.  She loves to hop around and eat grass.  She also enjoys carrots and watermelon and especially bananas.  		\n\nIf this game goes well, I am going to use the money to buy a live webcam so you can see Floppsy all the time.	</string>	<string name="AboutMeText">Hi I am Juliet!  I am age 9.  This is my first real game so please let me know what you think of it.  The best way to leave feedback is on the fluffle facebook page.		</string>  <string name="Error_Title">Error</string>  <string name="No_Fluffle_Cloud_Msg">Could not connect to the Fluffle cloud!  Check your network and then try again later...</string>  <string name="Connection_Err_Btn">bummer</string>  <string name="Sell_Bunny_Title">Sell Bunny</string>  <string name="Sell_Bunny_Btn">Sell</string>  <string name="Sell_Bunny_Cancel">nevermind</string>  <string name="Sell_Bunny_Msg">You can sell your bunny to the adoption center.  Then other people can adopt it!  Do you want to sell this {0} for {1} carrots?</string>  <string name="Bunny_Sale_Failed_Title">Sale Failure</string>  <string name="Bunny_Sale_Failed_Msg">Sorry, we were unable to sell your cute bunny.  Try again later.</string>  <string name="Bunny_Sale_Failed_Btn">oh well</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Title">Catch Failed!</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Gone_Msg">Sorry, the bunny is no longer there.</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Gone_Btn">sad face</string>  <string name="Too_Many_Bunnies">You have too many bunnies in this field.  No more will fit!  Hint:  you can sell bunnies for carrots or trade them with friends.</string>  <string name="Too_Many_Bunnies_Btn">makes sense</string>    <string name="Catch_Failed_Funds_Msg">You don\'t have enough carrots to trade for that bunny</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Funds_Btn">oh well</string>  <string name="Catch_Title">Catching a Bunny!</string>  <string name="Catch_Paid_Msg">Catch this bunny for {0} carrots?</string>  <string name="Catch_Paid_OK_Btn">Spend those carrots</string>  <string name="Catch_Cancel_Btn">nevermind</string>  <string name="Catch_Free_Msg">Catch this cute bunny?</string>  <string name="Catch_Free_OK_Btn">Catch It!</string>  <string name="Catch_Success_Title">Success</string>  <string name="Catch_Success_Msg">Enjoy your new bunny!</string>  <string name="Catch_Success_Btn">of course</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Title">oh well</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Unknown_Msg">Something went wrong.  Maybe try again?</string>  <string name="Catch_Failed_Unknown_Btn">will do</string>  <string name="Rename_Title">Rename Bunny</string>  <string name="Rename_Msg">What do you want to name this cute bunny?</string>  <string name="Rename_Err_Msg">Sorry, only the original owner can name a bunny!</string>  <string name="Rename_Err_Btn">bummer</string>  <string name="ok_btn">ok</string>  <string name="cancel_btn">cancel</string>  <string name="Unamed_Bunny">Unnamed Bunny</string>  <string name="Adoption_Agency">Adoption Agency</string>  <string name="Confirm_Adoption_Title">Confirm Adoption</string>  <string name="Confirm_Adoption_Prompt">Are you sure you want to adopt this bunny for {0} carrots?</string>  <string name="Adoption_Accepted_Title">Adoption Accepted</string>  <string name="Adoption_Declined_Title">Adoption Declined</string>  <string name="Adoption_Cancel_Btn">nevermind</string>  <string name="Adoption_OK_Btn">Adopt!</string>  <string name="Adoption_Lack_Funds">Sorry, you do not have enough carrots to adopt this bunny</string>  <string name="Adoption_Lack_Funds_Confirm">Oh well</string>  <string name="Adoption_Worked">Enjoy your new cute bunny!</string>  <string name="Adoption_Worked_Btn">Happiness!</string>  <string name="Adoption_Failed">Sorry, the adoption did not go through</string>  <string name="Adoption_Failed_Btn">Oh well</string>  <string name="New_Image_Msg">New Profile Image</string>  <string name="From_Camera_Msg">From Camera</string>  <string name="From_Gallery_Msg">From Gallery</string>  <string name="Delete_Current_Msg">Delete Current Photo</string>  <string name="Profile_Title">Your Profile</string>    <string name="Username_Msg">Unable to change username.  Make sure your username is unique.  Try an email address for best results</string>   <string name= "username_Btn">will do</string>    <string name="Nickname_Msg">Unable to change nickname.  Maybe try again later?</string>    <string name="Nickname_Btn">umm.. ok...</string>    <string name="Must_Change_Pwd_Msg">You must change your password when you first change your username.  Enter the new password now:</string>    <string name="Change_Pwd_Msg">Enter the new password now:</string>    <string name="Change_Pwd_Title">Change password</string>   <string name= "Change_Btn_Title">Change</string>    <string name="Change_Username_Err_Msg">Unable to change username.  Make sure your username is unique.  Try an email address for best results</string>    <string name="Change_Username_Err_Btn">will do</string>    <string name="Login_Title">Login</string>    <string name="Login_Prompt">Do you want to sign in to an existing account?</string>   <string name= "Login_Btn">signin</string>    <string name="Profile_Title">{0}\'s Profile</string>    <string name="Profile_Title_Unknown">Your Profile</string>    <string name="Login_Failure_Title">Sign in Failed</string>    <string name="Login_Failure_msg">Unable to sign in.  Check username and password.</string>    <string name="Login_Failure_btn">alright</string>  <string name="test_banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3804966396167875/6493407748</string>  <string name="test_interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3804966396167875/7970140948</string>  <string name="test_reward_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3804966396167875/4737472946</string>  <string name="Timeout_Msg">Done (ending in {0} seconds)</string>	<!-- for tutorial -->	<string name="skip_tutorials">skip tutorials</string>	<string name="tutorial_title">Tutorial</string>	<string name="click_bunny_tutorial">Welcome to Fluffle!  You already have one bunny, hopping around.  Tap it to get started!</string>	<string name="button_details_tutorial">Most of the time bunnies just eat grass.  But you can click on Feed to give your bunny a carrot.  After enough carrots, it will grow to the next size.</string>	<string name="bunny_grow_tutorial">Your bunny grew!  Now that it is no longer a baby, it can breed with other bunnies.  To get more bunnies, click the Adopt button.</string>	<string name="bunny_toss_tutorial">You can loan a bunny to a friend by tossing it to their phone.  Click the toss button on your phone to toss a button, and have your friend press catch on their phone to catch it.  Sharing is super fun!</string>	<string name="bunny_pet_tutorial">Bunnies love to be petted.  Tap your bunny to pet it.  Happy bunnies are more likely to breed!</string>	<string name="bunny_breed_tutorial">Male and female bunnies of the same size and breed have a chance to have babies.  The bigger and happier they are, the more likely it is.  Each girl bunny can have one baby every day.</string>	<string name="bunny_catch_tutorial">Need another bunny?  Borrow from a friend!  Have your friend toss a bunny to you, and then press catch.  When the camera starts, point the camera at your friend\'s phone.</string>	<string name="sell_bunny_tutorial">Need carrots?  You can sell a bunny back to the adoption agency.  Larger bunnies sell for more than smaller ones!</string>	<string name="buy_carrots_tutorial">Short on carrots?  You get more every day you play.  If you are in a hurry, click the carrots button to go to the store</string>	<string name="carrot_shop_tutorial">You can buy carrots for real money here.  When you buy carrots, you support fluffle!  Thanks in advance!!!</string>	<string name="adoption_store_tutorial">Adopt more bunnies here!\n  If you want to have baby bunnies, be sure to get a bunny of the same breed but opposite gender from the bunny you already have.  Bigger bunnies and rare bunnies cost more than babies.</string>	<string name="profile_tutorial">In profile you can change your profile photo and nickname.  These show up on the leaderboards!  You can also change your username and password.  That will let you log in to Fluffle from another phone.  Always keep your username and password private.</string>	<string name="rename_tutorial">Click the name of your bunny to rename it.  Once a bunny is named, only the person who named it can change that name - even if the bunny is adopted by someone else!</string>	</resources>