<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, Click Me!</string>
	<string name="app_name">Fluffle</string>
	<string name="test">test</string>

	<string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
	
	<string name="Game_Menu">Bunny Garden</string>
	<string name="Profile_Menu">Profile</string>
	<string name="Leaderboards_Menu">Leaderboards</string>
	<string name="Cam_Menu">Live Bunny Cam!</string>
	<string name="About_Menu">About Fluffle</string>
	<string name="AboutFluffleText">Here is everything you would ever want to know about fluffle.
		\n\nYou start with one bunny.  Tap it to select it.  This will show you info about the bunny.  
		Then tap the feed button to feed your bunny a carrot.  That will make it grow.  It is size 1 to start.  
		After 10 carrots it will be size 2.  Each size takes more carrots.  Large bunnies are easier to breed. 		\n\nYou get carrots every day you play.  You can also buy them in the carrot store as an in-app purchase. 		\n\nIf you want more bunnies, you can adopt them for carrots from the adoption center.  You can also get 
		bunnies by breeding them.  You need a male and female of the same breed and size to have babies.  
		Happy bunnies and large bunnies are more likely to breed.  Note that a mommy bunny can only have one baby per day. 		\n\nYou can also TRADE bunnies with  your friends.  To do this, tap the bunny and press the Trade button.  
		This will show a barcode.  Then have your friend press the trade button on their screen to start the camera.  
		If they point it at your barcode, they will get your bunny!  Try it, it is super fun.  
		You can also trade bunnies over a video call. 		\n\nWhat else?  Click the bunny\'s name to rename it.  Every bunny needs a name.  You can also go to the profile 
		to set your own name. </string>
		<string name="AboutFloppsyText">Floppsy is my bunny.  She is a Mini-lop.  She loves to hop around and eat grass.  She also enjoys carrots and watermelon and especially bananas.  
		\n\nIf this game goes well, I am going to use the money to buy a live webcam so you can see Floppsy all the time.
	</string>

	<string name="AboutMeText">Hi I am Juliet!  I am age 9.  This is my first real game so please let me know what you think of it.  The best way to leave feedback is on the fluffle facebook page.
		</string>
</resources>
